

About Me

A pro-active, hardworking, enthusiastic person with over 10 years retail industry experience.

Known for being calm under pressure and is a big believer in using common sense & initiative to make forward moving decisions.

Moved to Stockholm 4 years ago, with the idea of exploring passions and creating new opportunities.

Key Skills

MS Office - Word, PowerPoint,
Outlook, Excel.
Windows & Mac hardware &
software.
Logistics & Operations.
Project Management.
Event Management & Promotion.
DJ.
Music & Audio Production.

Languages

English (Mother Tongue)
Swedish (Working)

IVAN LUPAKA

STORE LOGISTICS MANAGER +46720330726. lupaka91@gmail.com

Work Experience

COS Stockholm Biblioteksgatan – Store Logistics Manager August 2019 – Present

Main responsibilities include

- Securing delivery and efficient stock levels in the store.
- Maintain stock levels & stockrooms at all times.
- Analyse selling and pro-actively adjust stock levels and stockroom accordingly.
- Train team and other members of staff on stockroom routines.
- Support area team with rollout of new projects.

Freelance DJ & Event Promoter May 2015 – Present

This role requires me to think about the best methods to promote myself as a brand, think one step ahead in order to find unique ideas, concepts and art, project manager at the level of ensuring various components of one big puzzle come together to create a successful event.

Education

London Metropolitan University 2009-2012: Sports Science BSc ***

City & Islington College 2007-2009: Sports Science BTEC Edmonton County School 2003-2007: 7 GCSE's (A-C grades)